Mak Mendelson UI / UX / Visual & Graphic Design

in linkedin.com/in/makmendelson/ 🤳 443.854.0819

MaltF4WillHelp

forekast.github.io



mak.mendelson (at) gmail (dot) com

Summary

Spirited and multifaceted Designer with 10+ years of experience in the development of effective, appealing, and easy-to-use websites & software applications. At CANDA Solutions, completely revitalized the look & feel of their site and products, pleasing clients with attractive new designs and improved user experience. Skilled in User Experience, User Interface, Visual, and Graphic Designs.

Skills English • Russian • Spanish

User Experience Design • User Interface Design • Visual Design • Graphic Design • Usability • UX Testing Adobe Illustrator • Adobe Photoshop • Front-End Web Design • HTML • CSS • Javascript • Agile • JIRA Git • Wireframing • Product Development • Game Design Game Development • Concept Art

Experience

Independent Contractor

CANDA Solutions, LLC.

February 2017 — Present http://candasolutions.com

- Designed, implemented, and maintained Wordpress sites:
 - http://freshhaystack.com/ http://persec.express/home/ http://candasolutions.com/
- Designed & Wireframed mock-ups, and implemented Front-End design for an online Dashboard for Employee Management, Onboarding, and Continuous Investigations
 - o Adobe Illustrator, HTML, CSS, working knowledge of Javascript and jQuery, Bootstrap
- Produced numerous detailed visual and business aids, allowing CANDA to demonstrate to their clients, with clarity, the inner workings of the products and services they offer
 - Marketing, Presentations, Show booth materials, Digital and Printed aids, Branding
 - Consulted on Mobile application design

User Interface Consultant and Tester

Buchanan & Edwards

December 2014 — June 2016 http://buchanan-edwards.com/

- Consulted, generated high-fidelity mock-ups, and tested User Interfaces in the development of a Knowledge Management Tool web application for the Department of State
- Collaborated with Business Analysts to collect, define, and document client requirements
- Collaborated with Developers to determine best implementation strategies, and to ensure product is inline with current design mock-ups
- Developed Branding and Stationary
- Had **DOD SECRET clearance** (EXPIRED June 2018)

Co-Founder and Visual Artist

Gradient Studios, LLC.

April 2010 — February 2014 http://www.gradientstudios.com

- Co-founded Gradient Studios, LLC. right out of college
- Developed Start-to-Finish, and Shipped two games of our own Intellectual Property
- Determined and Designed aesthetics for several games
- Created UI and game assets for several games
- Created promotional material: trailer/gameplay videos, posters, booth design
- Assisted in securing seed funding from Accomplice (formerly of Altas Ventures)

Education

Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute

2006 - 2010

BS, Games & Simulation Arts & Sciences, Concentration in Electronic Arts

Gilman School 2002 - 2006